# TZE FUNG JIM LUNG

1067, 59th Street, Brooklyn, NY 11219

Tel: (917) 214 – 0908 | fung10\_91@hotmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/tze-fung-lung-0a9111164/

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

Bilingual master graduate in data science with data analysis experience seeking a challenging position in the data analysis and engineering field where relevant expertise can be utilized

## **SKILLS**

Excellent working knowledge of R and Python for analysis and Data Science skills. Other areas of expertise include data scraping, data cleaning and imputation, data visualization, data mining and modeling, machine learning, Hadoop, Mathematics and statistics programming. BI analysis tool – Tableau, Looker, Mode and Google data Studio. Foreign language: Cantonese and Mandarin

Work Sample: <a href="https://fung1091.shinyapps.io/profile/">https://fung1091.shinyapps.io/profile/</a>

# **EDUCATION**

Master's Degree of Data Science at City University of New York (CUNY) (April 2019, GPA: 3.9)

BEng in Manufacturing Informatics and Systems Engineering from City University of Hong Kong

**Bachelor of Health Science** from RMIT University

## **EXPERIENCE**

Sales Operation Specialist – Center Plan Healthy Living (CPHL), New York, NY Dec. 2020 – Now

- Conducted Data Reporting analysis to generate daily, weekly and monthly visualization report
- Analyzed internal and external data (CMS gov)
- Work Sample: https://datastudio.google.com/u/0/reporting/5238bd99-da45-4c09-a3de-d5d0964ca0f4/page/1M

## Data Analyst – ONKIN CONSULTANT INC., New York, NY

Jul. 2019 - Nov.2020

- Work as Data Visualization modeler to leadership and market teams on strategic, organizational, and operational projects
- Build new dashboards on specific sales KPIs. Collaborate with the business operations team to audit and enhance sales specific Tableau and R Shiny dashboards.

## Intern (Data Team) - Kasisto, New York, NY

Jan. 2019 – Apr. 2019

- Improved and extracted the data sourcing pipeline and the natural language in chat-bot
- Developed and supported of a wide range of data transformations and migrations
- Constructed custom ETL processes

#### Co-Founder – Newinsock.com, New York, NY

Jan. 2017 – Dec. 2018

Dec. 2015 – Dec. 2016

• Conducted sourcing for products to ensure constant and timely supply of inventory; coordinated shipping and professional packaging for product orders; provided detailed follow-through and after sales service for customer satisfaction

# Safety Officer - PCCW Solutions, Hong Kong

• Organized details and workflow of a safety and health training program

- Performed daily inspection for various parts of the project and recorded all documentations and procedures involved
- Prepared detailed training records, inspection reports, inspection photos, drill reports and accident records

#### **QUALIFICATIONS AND CREDENTIALS**

Real Estate License (Jan. 2018); Graduate Member – Institution of Occupational Safety and Health (2014)